{
	"games" : [
		{
		    "questions" : [
		        {
		            "question" : "The first step before growing crops is _________ of the soil.",
		            "content" : [
		                "Fertilisation",
		                "Plantation",
		                "Watering",
						"Preparation"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 3
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "Damaged seeds would __________ water.",
		            "content" : [
		                "Sink in",
		                "Rupture in",
						"Float on",
		                "None of these above"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 2
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "Which of the following is not a rabi crop?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Mustard",
		                "Gram",
		                "Wheat",
		                "Rice"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 3
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "The main source of irrigation is:",
		            "content" : [
		                "Rainfall",
		                "Tubewell",
		                "Wells",
		                "River"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 0
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "It is used for loosening of the soil:",
		            "content" : [
		                "Cultivator",
		                "Plough",
		                "Funnel",
		                "Tractor"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 1
		        },
				{
				    "correct": 3,
				    "content": [
				        "Insects",
				        "Bacteria",
				        "Pest",
				        "Fungus"
				    ],
				    "question": "Fungicides are used to kill:"
				},
				{
				    "correct": 3,
				    "content": [
				        "Crop Rotation",
				        "Farming",
				        "Winnowing",
				        "Broadcasting"
				    ],
				    "question": "Scaterring of seeds is called:"
				},
				{
				    "correct": 0,
				    "content": [
				        "NH3",
				        "H2O",
				        "Al2(SO4)2",
				        "None of the above"
				    ],
				    "question": "Formula of Ammonia is:"
				},
				{
				    "correct": 1,
				    "content": [
				        "Agriculture",
				        "Symbiosis",
				        "Nitogen-Fixing",
				        "Nodules"
				    ],
				    "question": "Working together for mutual benifits is called:"
				},
				{
				    "correct": 3,
				    "content": [
				        "Farmers",
				        "Oxygen",
				        "Plants",
				        "Cyanobacteria"
				    ],
				    "question": "Nitogen cycle is carried out by:"
				},
				{
				    "correct": 2,
				    "content": [
				        "Made",
				        "By",
				        "Sharad",
				        "Kumar Singh"
				    ],
				    "question": "You Won!"
				}
		    ]
		}
	]
}